# Alexandra Nunez

Cell phone: 7862196846 <u>alex219mn@yahoo.com</u> www.linkedin.com/in/AlexMN

### **Career Overview**

An energetic and hospitable professional with six years of experience managing fast-paced, high volume restaurants with eight total years of catering to consumer needs as a customer service specialist; Proficient in multi-tasking under high pressure environments. Highly experienced in verbal and non-verbal communication with keen attention to detail; and a sales driven attitude catered to each individual and the brands focus always in mind.

## **Career History**

Bolay LLC Pembroke Pines, Miami Lakes, FL

July 2018-Current

#### **Salary Leader**

Recruited to lead a team for a growing brand "Bolay" being fully devoted to the expansion of this companies vision and principals as a restauranteur and "business owner." The qualities I've brought to this company are those of a seasoned and dedicated leader that focuses on the guest experience and protection of the brand.

- Effective communication with all staff, suppliers, support team and founders; implementation
  of sales building tactics and support communications.
- Expense and revenue monitoring and management via third party software; Tracking PnL's, by following yearly, monthly and weekly trends; Analyzation of consumer trends throughout each period.
- Assessing our costs vs. sales based off of monthly forecasts; completing daily sales reports and monthly audits that optimize proactive sales periods and budget goals.
- Exceeding all customer requests; Tailoring to each individuals needs with fast and proper resolution practices, developing customer trust.
- Responsible for overseeing all customer escalations via third party delivery services (Uber, Doordash, Postmates etc. and resolving all in-store occurrences; Trouble shooting all third party and tech related issues.
- Proven ability to efficiently coordinate work activities to meet multiple challenging demands
- Ensuring compliance with licensing, hygiene, health and safety legislation/guidelines.
- Sales building through in-store marketing including event planning, community outreach and donations; vast involvement in the community, building relationships and brand awareness.
- Revitalized training practices for new store openings; Created training tools that executed smooth transitions between new hires and staff members.
- Participation in all support related communication meetings via zoom enabling clear direction for all the leadership teams in South Florida.

## **Assistant General Manager**

Promoted to Kitchen Manager after six months of successful performance as a team member followed by a Service Manager position and furthermore as the Assistant General Manager supervising thirty or more employees during AM and PM shifts.

- Conveyed leadership mentoring through one on one conversations with all team members and trainees for in-store/out of store leadership positions.
- Execution of all staff schedules including onboarding for all new hires using third party systems; implementation of training and developmental tools.
- Presenting daily reports evaluate cost vs. sales trends, labor and inventory stock counts.
- Completion of daily operational reports including SMG guest assessments of quality and overall experience; Implemented spreadsheet keeping track of all less than satisfactory experiences and arranged call backs for each guest.
- Proper observation of specs from all vendors with close reporting and tracking of vendor resolutions; building relationships in the area to further supporting small businesses.
- Collaborations with other brands to further expand companies vision; This included working with local breweries and farms to bring in high quality ingredients and supporting the community. Evaluation of all guest desires and companies outputs.

# Cabo Flats Doral, FL

Server/Bartender

Jan 2018-June 2018

- Executing excellent customer service with focused attention on guests needs.
- Up-selling products with higher profit margins with company goals always in mind.
- Carefully listening to orders while making suggestive offers on food and beverages.
- Having complete knowledge of food and beverage menu as well as relative promotional items; Providing orders in a timely manner with proper presentation.
- Properly following company and state policies and hygienic practices.
- Properly following all sanitation procedures, safety recommendations and CDC guides.
- Upholding and completing side work while helping others.
- Properly maintaining liquor stocks throughout shift as well as opening and closings.

#### **EDUCATION**

Miami Dade College / Hialeah Gardens High School

August 2010- May 2014

High School Diploma

#### **Recording Connection**

January 2018-January 2019

• Certified in Music production and Sound Engineering

#### **Skills**

Experienced with Ableton Live Suite 10, Protools, Adobe editing softwares, Excel and Microsoft softwares.

Avid with computer and telecommunication applications.

Bilingual: Fluent in both English, Spanish (verbal and writing.)